# William Tyler Brown

3621 Brownsboro Road 203B Louisville, KY 40207 • (502)554-6662 • wtbrown1992@gmail.com

in: https://www.linkedin.com/in/williamtylerbrown/

## **CAREER GBJECTIVE**

Looking to secure a position as a Technology Consultant with Humana, Inc. in Information Technology – Data Analytics Architecture area with two years of experience in project planning, application development and support, and data management as a Technology Intern with Enterprise Messaging Data Analytics and Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services Audit & Compliance IT teams in cooperation with business clients.

	CORE COM	PETENCIES		
Team Building	Future Planning		Creative Thinking	
Collaborative Working	Planning and Organization		Resourcefulness	
Change Management	Persuasive Techniques		Problem Solving	
Data Management	Research		<b>Identifying Patterns</b>	
	TECHNIC	CAL SKILLS		
<u>Languages</u>	<u>Tools</u>		Operating Systems	
SQL	Microsoft SQL Server	<b>Team Foundation Server</b>	Windows	
PL/SQL	TOAD for Oracle	SharePoint Designer	Linux	
C#	Microsoft Office	TortoiseGit & Git	Unix	
HTML	Visual Studio	QlikView		

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

## Humana Inc., Louisville, KY

Technology Intern, Aug 2016 - present

- 1. Develop and offer support for automation project that generates universe data quality compliance reports and aggregated source files from business input files using TOAD for Oracle, Microsoft SQL Server Management Studio, Visual Studio, and Informatica.
- 2. Developed and designed SharePoint project for Information Management & Analytics VP linking the SharePoint sites of areas within her department using SharePoint Designer.
- 3. Developed and maintained QlikView and Tableau reports using Microsoft SQL Server and TOAD for Oracle for Enterprise Messaging team with two other interns.

#### Chop Shop Salads, Louisville, KY

Manager/Employee, Aug 2014 – Aug 2015

1. Local salad restaurant where I prepared portions before opening and served throughout the day and night.

# O'Charley's, Lexington, KY

Server, Jun 2013 - May 2014

1. Waited on tables while enrolled in courses.

## **Cutco & Vector Marketing**, Louisville, KY

Entry Level Sales Representative, Jun 2011 - Aug 2011

- 1. Sales Rep for a kitchen knife distribution and marketing company.
- 2. Received professional training for business strategies and demonstration techniques for Cutco products.

#### **EDUCATION**

## University of Louisville, College of Business, Louisville, KY

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration:

Computer Information Systems with Information Security Concentration

May 2018

- Developed and implemented an improved web application in ASP.NET Model-View-Controller for Kentucky Horsemen's Benevolent & Protective Association. Website URL provided upon request.
- Analyzed IT structure of above organization to gather requirements for web application project.

### Saint Xavier High School, Louisville, KY

May 2011